<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Computer Hacking 101</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Computer Hacking 101</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Feb 15, 2023, update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/feb152023update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/feb152023update/</guid>
      <description>move to another server I am now hosting this website on my own server located at my house. I am using Cloudflare tunnel, Cloudflare catch, docker, GitHub, and Jenkins to create and host this and my personal site. I will make multiple videos on how to do this. It took me a while to set it up correctly.&#xA;still fixing a few issues with the website I still need to fix a few more issues on this website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>What is Docker: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/whatisdocker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/whatisdocker/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, the use of Docker has skyrocketed in popularity, especially within the development community. Docker is an open-source containerization platform that simplifies the process of building, deploying, and managing applications. It provides a lightweight, portable, and self-sufficient runtime environment that can run on any machine. In this article, we will dive deep into Docker, its components, how it works, and its benefits.&#xA;Understanding Docker Architecture Docker architecture comprises several components that work together to provide a complete containerization solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Turn Off Microsoft Spying and Protect Your Privacy</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/windows/turn_off_microsoft_spying/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/windows/turn_off_microsoft_spying/</guid>
      <description>Title: How to Turn Off Microsoft Spying and Protect Your Privacy&#xA;With the rise of technology, privacy has become a major concern for many people. Microsoft has faced criticism for collecting user data through its products and services, but don&#39;t worry, you can take control of your privacy and turn off Microsoft&#39;s data collection with just a few simple steps.&#xA;Step 1: Review Privacy Settings in Windows 10 The first step to turning off Microsoft spying is to review your privacy settings in Windows 10.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install docker, Docker Compose, and portainer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/install-docker-compose-portainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/install-docker-compose-portainer/</guid>
      <description>Docker is a popular platform for building, shipping, and running distributed applications. Docker Compose is a tool for defining and running multi-container Docker applications. Portainer is a management tool for Docker that makes it easy to manage your containers, images, networks, and volumes. In this article, we&#39;ll show you how to install these tools on a Linux server.&#xA;Prerequisites Before we get started, make sure that you have a Linux server set up and that you have administrative access to that server.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We change the theme with other updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/changthetheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/changthetheme/</guid>
      <description>I have modified the appearance of this website and am currently in the process of refining some of its pages, such as the contact page, while also incorporating a new copy-and-paste feature for ease of code sharing. Please note that further changes to the website&#39;s aesthetics may occur.&#xA;In addition, I am diligently working on the completion of a tutorial video regarding the utilization of syncthing, which will likely be accompanied by supplementary documentation on this platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Set Up a Secure GitHub Account and Use Security Features</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorial/github/createingSecureGithubAccount/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Mar 2022 12:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorial/github/createingSecureGithubAccount/</guid>
      <description>GitHub is a popular platform used by developers to collaborate on projects and share code. However, as with any online platform, it&#39;s important to take steps to secure your account and protect your data. In this guide, we&#39;ll walk you through the steps you can take to set up a secure GitHub account and use security features.&#xA;Create a Strong Password When creating your GitHub account, make sure to use a strong password that is not easily guessable.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Syncthing on Windows</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/syncthing/installing-syncthing-on-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Feb 2022 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/syncthing/installing-syncthing-on-windows/</guid>
      <description>To Install Syncthing on Windows there are two ways of installing it. One is with synctrazor which I will walkthrough below. It also comes with the benefit of having a GUI(Graphical User Interface).&#xA;1. Download Synctrazor The first step is to download Synctrazor. You can download it from the following link.&#xA;1https://github.com/canton7/SyncTrayzor/#installation` When you go to the page you need to click on Download SyncTrayzorSetup-x64.exe. This will download the executable file.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install Syncthing on Linux</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/docs/syncthing/installing-syncthing-on-linux/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/docs/syncthing/installing-syncthing-on-linux/</guid>
      <description>Step 1 add Syncthing repo to apt sources Syncthing isn’t available to install using the default repo. So the first step is adding syncthing repo to our apt sources so we can install it on our computer. We need to open up a terminal and run the following command.&#xA;1echo &amp;#34;deb https://apt.syncthing.net/ syncthing stable&amp;#34; | sudo tee /etc/apt/sources.list.d/syncthing.list Step 2 Installing curl We must ensure we have curl installed to install the syncthing PGP key.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dropbox vs Syncthing Which should you choose?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/syncthing/dropbox-vs-syncthing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jan 2022 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/syncthing/dropbox-vs-syncthing/</guid>
      <description>In the video below I will explain the differnece between Dropbox and Syncthing. It will explain why I went with syncthing.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first blog post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/firstblogpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/firstblogpost/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and welcome to the inaugural post on the Computer Hacking 101 website. In this blog, we aim to keep you informed about our ongoing projects and updates to our YouTube channel and website.&#xA;As part of our efforts to enhance the website&#39;s functionality, we have transitioned from WordPress to Hugo, a contemporary and robust website builder. As we continue to refine the website&#39;s design, some changes may occur over time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Search</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/search/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/search/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
