<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Computer Hacking 101</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Computer Hacking 101</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Feb 15, 2023, update</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/feb152023update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/feb152023update/</guid>
      <description>move to another server I am now hosting this website on my own server located at my house. I am using Cloudflare tunnel, Cloudflare catch, docker, GitHub, and Jenkins to create and host this and my personal site. I will make multiple videos on how to do this. It took me a while to set it up correctly.&#xA;still fixing a few issues with the website I still need to fix a few more issues on this website.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>We change the theme with other updates</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/changthetheme/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/changthetheme/</guid>
      <description>I have modified the appearance of this website and am currently in the process of refining some of its pages, such as the contact page, while also incorporating a new copy-and-paste feature for ease of code sharing. Please note that further changes to the website&#39;s aesthetics may occur.&#xA;In addition, I am diligently working on the completion of a tutorial video regarding the utilization of syncthing, which will likely be accompanied by supplementary documentation on this platform.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The first blog post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/blog/firstblogpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/blog/firstblogpost/</guid>
      <description>Greetings and welcome to the inaugural post on the Computer Hacking 101 website. In this blog, we aim to keep you informed about our ongoing projects and updates to our YouTube channel and website.&#xA;As part of our efforts to enhance the website&#39;s functionality, we have transitioned from WordPress to Hugo, a contemporary and robust website builder. As we continue to refine the website&#39;s design, some changes may occur over time.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
