<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Docker on Computer Hacking 101</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/categories/docker/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Docker on Computer Hacking 101</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/categories/docker/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Docker: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/whatisdocker/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/whatisdocker/</guid>
      <description>In recent years, the use of Docker has skyrocketed in popularity, especially within the development community. Docker is an open-source containerization platform that simplifies the process of building, deploying, and managing applications. It provides a lightweight, portable, and self-sufficient runtime environment that can run on any machine. In this article, we will dive deep into Docker, its components, how it works, and its benefits.&#xA;Understanding Docker Architecture Docker architecture comprises several components that work together to provide a complete containerization solution.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Install docker, Docker Compose, and portainer</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/install-docker-compose-portainer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2023 19:54:29 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/tutorials/docker/install-docker-compose-portainer/</guid>
      <description>Docker is a popular platform for building, shipping, and running distributed applications. Docker Compose is a tool for defining and running multi-container Docker applications. Portainer is a management tool for Docker that makes it easy to manage your containers, images, networks, and volumes. In this article, we&#39;ll show you how to install these tools on a Linux server.&#xA;Prerequisites Before we get started, make sure that you have a Linux server set up and that you have administrative access to that server.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
